<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-23T20:22:18-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">hi there!</title><subtitle>welcome to my portfolio. my name is vivian cheung, and i'm an enthusiast of great experiences. :)</subtitle><author><name>vivian cheung</name></author><entry><title type="html">journey: phnom penh</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cambodia.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="journey: phnom penh" /><published>2020-07-07T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-07T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cambodia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cambodia.html">&lt;h6 id=&quot;originally-written-for-impulse-online-now-defunct&quot;&gt;Originally written for impulse online (now defunct).&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only when I was boarding the flight to Phnom Penh, the largest city and capital of Cambodia, I realized that I honestly had no idea what to expect. Almost 23 years after our family’s immigration to Canada, my mom and grandma were finally going back home to the country they were born and raised in, after being forced out so many years ago. A place that I have never heard any stories of until now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/cambodia/photo_1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;my-grandmothers-younger-brother&quot;&gt;My grandmother’s younger brother.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found out that my mom grew up in her grandmother’s house in the countryside (to this day, I still don’t know what this area is called). She wass sent there from the capital because her parents were too busy trying to make a living to take care of their six children. Overlooking a freshwater lake was her new home - identical to the other homes around it. She lived in a giant room where her entire family would cook their meals and sleep. Underneath the room was a tiny farm where they would raise poultry and swine. My great-grandmother’s family once thrived on acres and acres of land, which they would eventually lose during the Khmer War. To this day, only the house remains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/cambodia/photo_2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;children-playing-outside&quot;&gt;Children playing outside.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also found out how easy it was to feel disconnected in a city that should feel like a second home (after all, family is family, right?). But time in Cambodia moves slow. There’s no sense of urgency once you’ve reached your destination, but for some reason drivers in the city are always incredibly impatient. Like its surrounding countries, masses of bikes and scooters leave little room for anything else on the street, but luxury SUV’s dominate whatever space remains. Then there are the little things. Discretely bribing customs into approving your visas upon landing by hiding US dollars in your passport to hasten entry, your uncle carrying a gun with him every time we went out in public, realizing that there are differently coloured license plates to distinguish a citizen’s privilege.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/cambodia/photo_3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/cambodia/photo_4.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;top-my-great-grandmothers-house-in-the-countryside-bottom-my-grandmothers-eldest-sister&quot;&gt;Top: My great-grandmother’s house, in the countryside. Bottom: My grandmother’s eldest sister.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The countryside of Cambodia was definitely easier to adapt to than the bustle in Phnom Penh. There was no A/C, but sleeping under mosquito nets on the floor, surrounded by eight other bodies in the same small room was surprisingly comfortable - it just felt right. If you looked through the cracks of the wood floor, you could watch the chickens sleeping, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/cambodia/photo_5.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;a-relative-she-refused-any-money-we-tried-to-give-her-but-she-did-like-the-melon-candy-i-had-with-me-i-ended-up-giving-her-all-five-packs&quot;&gt;A relative. She refused any money we tried to give her, but she did like the melon candy I had with me. I ended up giving her all five packs.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Living was made beautiful by its lack of chaos and everyday simplicity. It acted as a memorandum - sometimes it isn’t necessary to look for signs of familiarity, or to become attached to a new place and actually feel at home. It reminded me of how my grandparents eventually relocated their family to live in the refugee camps of Vietnam, and to our lives in Vancouver now. A friendly reminder that home is not a physical entity, but being where your heart is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/cambodia/photo_6.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;dinner&quot;&gt;Dinner.&lt;/h6&gt;</content><author><name>vivian cheung</name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Originally written for impulse online (now defunct).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">live/play, a documentary miniseries with riot games</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/riot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="live/play, a documentary miniseries with riot games" /><published>2020-07-07T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-07T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/riot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/riot.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/liveplay1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-liveplay&quot;&gt;What is Live/Play?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live/Play is a documentary miniseries that explores stories sourced straight from the League of Legends community. As a video game with over 100 million active monthly players worldwide, Live/Play highlights twelve stories from Korea, Norway, Taiwan, the United States and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gamers don’t exactly have the best reputation for being positive, upstanding netizens. Live/Play aims to showcase stories that challenge players’ preconceived notions about each other and provide a deeper understanding and appreciation for the people in the League of Legends community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;challenges&quot;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/liveplay3.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;League of Legends isn’t just a game. Many players use the game as a medium to create, maintain, and strengthen their relationships with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took this into account, as well as factors such as culture, language, and region to inform how we would reach out to players, and how we would tell their stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data has shown that players in Korea, for instance, are very particular in how they consume their media and what kind of media they enjoy. In short: snappy, fun, and troll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of Live/Play’s goal to harness the passion and empathy in League of Legends players, using social media to reach out to players has a multitude of benefits. Not only are players able to share their stories with us, but the community-building nature of social media allowed them to share their stories with other players as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This helped to foster a sense of positivity in the community at the very introduction of Live/Play while beaconing the project as a representation of authentic storytelling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;social-media-plan-of-attack&quot;&gt;Social Media Plan of Attack&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Armed with an understanding of where our players tend to conglomerate online, I worked with teams across our nineteen offices around the world to create a multi-step social campaign to reach out to our demographic using tweets, Facebook, blogs, community influencers, and reddit. We asked players to respond to our prompts with their stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few examples of how I reached out to our community around the world:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/process2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/process3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/process4.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live/Play would have not been possible without harnessing the power of social media. Its immense reach in further depths of the community, as well as the ability to bring people together, is the only reason the research portion of the project was successful. All stories showcased in the documentary were made possible by the engagement of the League of Legends community, with players submitting their stories to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;supporting-metrics&quot;&gt;Supporting Metrics&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The success of this multi-step social media campaign can be measured in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Story submissions and engagement through social media and other supported platforms by players exceeded our goals by 1400%. It is never easy to ask anyone to share personal anecdotes about their own lives, especially with strangers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engagement around video content (views, average view time, click-through, social media, and player sentiment) also blew our expectations off the roof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Player perception of playing without vs. with friends (cooperation, fun, and their overall experience).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;not-just-for-players&quot;&gt;Not Just for Players&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/liveplay8.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also set up a plan to market the miniseries internally within Riot. I set up several viewing parties for the finale, hyping it up over the last week with email blasts, calendar invites, alternating cafeteria advertising, and promises of the feels. We wanted Rioters to advocate Live/Play and be able to have conversations with the players over social media, forums, and reddit too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;learnings&quot;&gt;Learnings&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/riot/rodger2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, the most fulfilling part of the entire process was receiving feedback from players and Rioters upon the miniseries’ release.  The documentary’s impact on player perception of the community, and seeing players bond over the different (and sometimes very difficult) topics touched upon in the miniseries, was incredibly powerful and rewarding. I’m so proud to have had the opportunity to give back to the community that I love so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;watch-the-miniseries-here&quot;&gt;watch the miniseries here:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=epWMZK6nHgI&quot;&gt;miniseries trailer&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RdoFNMFHt4Q&quot;&gt;series finale teaser&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;episode &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zxzemc87H_Y&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zRARu1oliFY&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8EERYW5KX-U&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-9EcHaL6f6g&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>vivian cheung</name></author><category term="projects" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">dialogue with velt</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/velt.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="dialogue with velt" /><published>2020-07-03T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-03T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/velt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/velt.html">&lt;h6 id=&quot;originally-written-and-photographed-for-impulse-online-now-defunct&quot;&gt;Originally written and photographed for impulse online (now defunct).&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/velt/download.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Launched just this September, VELT creates bags inspired by the lifestyle in Vancouver, Canada. Every VELT product is created with its user and environment in mind, with a substantial emphasis on functionality without sacrificing comfort or personal style. impulse had the opportunity to sit down with the minds behind VELT, Clayton Chan and Andy Tran, to talk about their growing label..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/velt/DSC06426.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-the-story-behind-velt&quot;&gt;What’s the story behind VELT?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: I first saw a place in the market when I was a student and shopping for a backpack. I couldn’t find a bag that was reasonably priced – a basic backpack would be around $60, and something that was unique would jump past the $200 price point. I didn’t feel like I could spend that kind of money while I was in school. This was before 2012, when Andy and I were already talking about creating something together. So we thought: “Why not do backpacks?” It’s something different: we’re into clothes, but we’re also into something that is strong, individual and unique. We wanted to make backpacks that represent who we are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: We wanted to create something that wasn’t t-shirts. Everyone does t-shirts. We figured doing backpacks and accessories is a good gateway for other things. People might say $95 for a backpack is expensive, but a lot of people put out $100 into buying a t-shirt. Once you invest in a backpack, you realize that your life just gets a little more organized. Spread the price out over two years and it becomes an investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/velt/DSC06552.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-did-you-two-meet&quot;&gt;How did you two meet?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: We met through mutual friends in high school. We always had homies that were kind of into clothes but not as much as we were, so we built our relationship around fashion and styling. We connected that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-velts-vision-and-philosophy&quot;&gt;What is VELT’s vision and philosophy?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: Minimalistic functionality without sacrificing comfort and to make an honest product. We have a love for high quality and unique products and we do the best we can to satisfy the customer at our price level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-your-influences&quot;&gt;What are your influences?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: From wearing what everyone wore in high school and realizing in post-secondary that we don’t actually like any of that shit. Honestly, we grew up wearing Ed Hardy, True Religion - stuff like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: We approach our products with a technical and modern approach. There’s brands out there that have more of a heritage kind of look and that’s not what we’re trying to do. In the end, there are only so many backpack shapes that you can do, so we’ll do that but with our own take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: If you look at Herschel, they do more of a heritage kind of look. And there’s Côte&amp;amp;Ciel which has a futuristic kind of look. We try to make a bag for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: In Vancouver, I was taking an hour bus ride every day just to go to school. A backpack is comfortable. f you have a long day and a lot of things to carry – a backpack offers the capacity to fulfill that need, and make it comfortable at the same time. I got a friend to test one of our samples. When he came back to us and he said, “Wow, what a difference it makes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-were-some-challenges-faced-in-starting-velt&quot;&gt;What were some challenges faced in starting VELT?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: We faced a lot of legal issues, logistics, and problems we didn’t expect to have when you start a company. But I’m glad that there are these problems to overcome, because they are definitely a huge learning experience for me and Andy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: There’s so much more to just designing and creating a product. We had to rent a U-Haul truck just to release our product from customs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: Our website issue – if you think it’s expensive to hire a professional web designer, try hiring an amateur. It’s usually better to put out those extra dollars. Our website got delayed for a whole month because of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-long-does-it-take-to-create-a-bag-from-the-design-to-the-production-and-testing-process&quot;&gt;How long does it take to create a bag? From the design, to the production and testing process.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: I work closely with the designer on the production process. I bounce ideas back and forth through Skype because he’s located in Hong Kong. He lets me know what will work and what won’t, but he’ll try to accommodate my requests. That’s why the sample process can take up to 4 months to complete. But at least you know you have a good product. He’ll send me 50 different fabrics and source out the ones I pick, which is really convenient because I don’t have to be in Hong Kong to do all of this. It takes a little bit longer, but at least I can stay in Vancouver. For production, there’s a factory who makes the bags for us – they ship the samples to test once they’re ready, and we just keep cycling this process until I’m happy with the final product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: Sometimes the samples don’t turn out to be what we expected. We had one bag where samples looked amazing but I remember looking at it during production and wondering what happened. There’s shape changes and stuff. One of these bags were supposed to be way wider, but we made it an inch smaller when we were placing units, and we’re so glad we did it. The bag turned out much better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: You have to test your own products. I think whenever a designer makes their own product, like clothing, they should know what happens after you’ve washed it 10 times. That’s important. I know when Andy and I test our bags, we use them hard and really try to test them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: I’ve used two of the bags for a good 14 months in the harsh Edmonton winter, and they survived the test of time. It’s pretty durable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/velt/DSC06391.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-next-for-velt-do-you-guys-plan-on-expanding-outside-of-bags&quot;&gt;What’s next for VELT? Do you guys plan on expanding outside of bags?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: I’m going to be going back to school next year for product design. I have an International Business degree, but I’m really into fashion and I only realized this after I graduated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: It’s good that the both of us have a business background. Being creative is one thing, but  we need to be able to sell our stuff and channel it in the right way. I do more of the brand management and marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: At the moment, we want to get into retailers so customers can get a feel for the product. I know they will be surprised at the quality and how it compares to competing brands. Outside of bags, I want to create a bigger product line, do 6-7 backpacks and accessories in the future. We’re not ready to do clothing until we’re happy with the capital that can be used to make something that we honestly love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy: Everyone does t-shirts and tries to do a fashion line but they don’t have the creativity or knowledge about anything like proportions. We figured doing backpacks and accessories would be good gateway for bigger things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people do t-shirts or their own fashion line but don’t have the knowledge about basic things like proportions. We wanted to start with backpacks and accessories as a gateway for bigger things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clayton: If Andy and I were to ever do clothing, I wouldn’t want to do it any less than the highest level of quality of the designers that we personally love. We wouldn’t cut corners in terms of quality and the same thing goes with our backpacks..&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>vivian cheung</name></author><category term="projects" /><summary type="html">Originally written and photographed for impulse online (now defunct).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">a ramen-iscing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ramen.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a ramen-iscing" /><published>2020-07-02T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-02T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ramen</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ramen.html">&lt;p&gt;(Sorry, not sorry for the pun.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wrapping up a work contract last September when I came upon some very inexpensive flights from LAX to NRT. After maybe twenty minutes of heavy deliberating and some phone calls to my best friend and parents for emotional support, I spontaneously booked a two-week return trip for one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two things that I remember very vividly about this trip. How gorgeous and warm Japan can be in November, and oh my god, the ramen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been very lucky to have lived in both LA and Vancouver, where the food scene is ever thriving and growing. And as a self-proclaimed ramen enthusiast, I’m also very lucky that both cities have much to offer in this realm of noodles. LA is home to Tsujita (both Annex and L.A.), Benten, and Ramen by Omae. In Vancouver, we have Marutama, Hida Takayama, and Taishoken, amongst others. And as good as these are (in a I-would-tank-traffic-and-wait-2-hours-to-eat-there-worthy), there are two kinds of ramen that I’ve still never tried up to this past trip to Japan - ones that I would book flights to Japan to eat again ASAP, if the opportunity ever showed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few personal prerequisites that determine the tastiness of a bowl. The broth must have depth, swirling together layers of umami and rich fat on your tongue. The noodles, are of course al dente, with a bouncy chew but not too much bite. The tamago must have a creamy, soft yolk that hints of shoyu. The smell is punchy, heavy, and overwhelming. That’s the kind of ramen I like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;nagi&quot;&gt;nagi&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/ramennagi.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niboshi ramen is, in one word, wild. It’s nothing like the traditional ramen soup bases of tonkotsu, shio, shoyu, or even miso. Instead, the soup is incredibly fishy, as the base is made of sardines. The broth is thick like gravy and heavy with the taste of sardines and pork, glittering of fat. The hand-made noodles, which comes in a variety of thicknesses, is the perfect vehicle to carry the broth . Food writer Kee Byung-Keun of the now defunct Lucky Peach says it best: “Niboshi […] is not for everybody: it is the liquid manifestation of dried baby sardines. There is a certain “must be this tall to ride” factor in stepping up to a bowl.” Not only is their ramen amazing, but entering the dim-lit restaurant and walking up the steepest of stairs that seemingly lead to nowhere will make you feel like you’re in your own dreamy Studio Ghibli film. Once you’re done, you’re probably going to walk out with some time shaved off your years, but I swear it’ll be worth it. It’s worth experiencing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/9nYA9QLRutttRgtW9&quot;&gt;google maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;abura-soba&quot;&gt;abura soba&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/aburasoba.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abura soba is also little different from your usual ramen suspects, and almost even more so than Nagi. Your ramen noodles won’t come with a broth, but it will come sitting on top of a gravy-like mixture made of a special shoyu sauce and pork fat. Topped with green onion, bamboo shoots, seaweed, cha shu, and a soft boiled egg, abura soba is the garlicky-spicy-tangy dream you never knew you absolutely needed. Once you’re handed your bowl of noodles, you add in however much chili oil, vinegar, and raw minced garlic of your choosing before mixing everything all together. It’s a refreshing change from regular ramen, but the immense pleasure of slurping the fat-coated noodles is just as enjoyable. Just don’t take your first date there, unless they’re into that stinky kinda thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abura Soba (literally named after the dish) is a chain with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tokyo-aburasoba.com/&quot;&gt;multiple locations&lt;/a&gt; all over Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>vivian cheung</name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">(Sorry, not sorry for the pun.)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">things that go bump in the night</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/lofi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="things that go bump in the night" /><published>2020-07-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/lofi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/lofi.html">&lt;p&gt;Sounds kinda dirty, but I’m actually talking about lo-fi hip hop. I’ve been a huge Nujabes fan ever since the Samurai Champloo days over a decade ago. Although I enjoy anything from classical to rap, instrumental hip hop has taken hold of a soft spot in my heart and still hasn’t let go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes hip hop lo-fi is the lack of perfection that is often found in highly produced music. Think scratches, hums, and unusual frequencies. The result? A jazzy, enchanting and bittersweet wave of nostalgia built from strong but slow beats. It’s also very reminiscent of the tunes that were played on Adult Swim back then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve found that late nights can be the best time to find some really great tunes, and I’ve linked some of my personal favorites below. Perfect for slow Sunday mornings, grinding out some video games, or even staying up to finish some work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/205531776&amp;amp;color=%23cecece&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;show_teaser=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/313534719&amp;amp;color=%23cecece&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;show_teaser=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>vivian cheung</name></author><category term="writing" /><summary type="html">Sounds kinda dirty, but I’m actually talking about lo-fi hip hop. I’ve been a huge Nujabes fan ever since the Samurai Champloo days over a decade ago. Although I enjoy anything from classical to rap, instrumental hip hop has taken hold of a soft spot in my heart and still hasn’t let go.</summary></entry></feed>